http://www.endfatigue.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Hi,
Sign In
Search form
Search
Hello,
Sign In
Home |
Sign In | Create Account |
Empty
View Cart (0 items)
$0.00
Checkout
| Help
HomeMy AccountSign In / Create AccountMy AccountShopping CartCFS & FibromyalgiaCFS & Fibromyalgia ExplainedS.H.I.N.E.® ProtocolWhat S.H.I.N.E.® Users SayHelp With Disability BenefitsFind a Trained PractitionerFind a Support GroupResearch StudiesHelpful LinksPrivate ConsultationsFAQShopShop By Health InterestShop By IngredientSee All Products A-Z20% Off with Auto ShipDr. T's BooksDr. T's FormulationsSale ItemsShipping and Return PoliciesHealth InterestsSpecific Health TopicsEnergy Analysis ProgramNutrition GuideVitamins, Minerals & HerbsAsk Dr. TSubmit a question to Dr. TAbout Dr. TMeet Dr. Teitelbaum About EndFatigue®Press CoverageContact UsMy AccountShopping CartShop By Health InterestShop By IngredientSee All Products A-ZShipping & Return PoliciesReturn to Main Site
Privacy Policy
We will never share your personal information with anybody.
The owners and operators of the website at https://www.endfatigue.com are committed to safeguarding your privacy. We believe that the best way to protect the privacy of users of www.endfatigue.com (the "Site") is to tell you what information we gather and ensure that you understand and consent to our uses of such information. We may occasionally modify the Privacy Policy and will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. You should check the policy frequently to read the changes. Please note that the Site contains links to and from other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites, and the information practices of those websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.
By accessing the Site, you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this website. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.
These terms are intended to fully comply with GDPR regulations. If you are accessing our Site from the European Union and have concerns about the thoroughness of our compliance, your should refrain from visiting our Site.
This Site Does Not Provide Medical Advice
This website is owned by From Fatigued to Fantastic, LLC ("FFTF"). The information provided at this website is intended for your general knowledge and educational purposes only and is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice or treatment. The information provided at this website is not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.
Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health care provider with any questions you may have regarding your health or a medical condition, or to discuss treatment options, including the use of prescription medications. Never disregard or delay seeking medical advice because of something you have read on this website or any other
website owned by FFTF.
Information provided on this site, and your use of this site, does not create a doctor-patient relationship. The information provided on this site is not intended to be a substitute for any information contained on the label or in the labeling of products recommended.
You should carefully review all product packaging, including instructions for use and precautionary statements, prior to using any product that you have purchased through this or any other FFTF website.
Information on this site and statements regarding dietary supplements have not been evaluated by the Food and Drug Administration and are not intended to diagnose, treat, cure, or prevent any disease.
Notice to Minors
This site is intended for use by adults only.
If you are under age 13, do not use this site and do not send us any personal information including your email.
If you would like to contact us, please ask your parent or legal guardian to contact us on your behalf.
Modifications
FFTF may revise these terms of service for its website at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these terms of service.
Limitations
In no event shall FFTF or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on FFTF's website, even if FFTF or a FFTF authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
Information We Collect
Log Data
When you visit our website, our servers may automatically log the standard data provided by your web browser. This data is considered "non-identifying information", as it does not personally identify you on its own. It may include your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and version, the pages you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on each page, and other details.
We may also collect data about the device you are using to access our website. This data may include the device type, operating system, unique device identifiers, device settings, and geo-location data. What we collect can depend on the individual settings of your device and software. We recommend checking the policies of your device manufacturer or software provider to learn what information they make available to us.
Personal Information
We may ask for personal information, such as name, email address, phone number, home mailing address, and payment information, but only as is necessary to process orders you place at our ecommerce store. We may also ask for your email address, but only in response to your request to sign up for our free newsletter.
This data is considered "identifying information," as it can personally identify you. We only request personal information relevant to providing you with a service, and only use it to help provide or improve this service.
How We Collect Information
We collect information by fair and lawful means, with your knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we're collecting it and how it will be used. You are free to refuse our request for this information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services without it.
How We Use Information
We may use a combination of identifying and non-identifying information to understand who our visitors are, how they use our services, and how we may improve their experience of our website in the future. We do not disclose the specifics of this information publicly, but may share aggregated and anonymised versions of this information, for example, in website and customer usage trend reports.
We may use your personal details to contact you with updates about our website and services, along with promotional content that we believe may be of interest to you. If you wish to opt out of receiving promotional content, you can follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided alongside any promotional correspondence from us.
For Social Media
When you engage with our content on or through third-party social networking
websites, plug-ins and applications, you may allow us to have access to certain
social media account information (e.g., name, username, email address, gender)
as determined by the settings of the social media services to deliver the
content or as part of the operation of the website, plug-in or application.
Social media platforms may collect information about your use of our services
and may notify other users of the platform about your activities on our
websites and mobile applications. Social media services may also use cookies or
other technologies to provide services or track your online activities over
time and across multiple websites and mobile applications. Your interactions
with social media features are governed by the respective privacy policies of
the companies providing the features.
For Other Uses We May Disclose to You
We may also use personal information with your consent, and as otherwise
permitted or required by law.
Data Processing and Storage
The personal information we collect is stored and processed in United States, or where we or our partners, affiliates and third-party providers maintain facilities. We only transfer data within jurisdictions subject to data protection laws that reflect our commitment to protecting the privacy of our users.
We only retain personal information for as long as necessary to provide a service, or to improve our services in future. While we retain this data, we will protect it within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. That said, we advise that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, and cannot guarantee absolute data security.
If you request your personal information be deleted, or where your personal information becomes no longer relevant to our operations, we will erase it from our system within a reasonable timeframe.
Third-Party Access to Information
We use third-party services for:
Analytics tracking
User authentication
Content marketing
Email marketing
Payment processing
These services may access our data solely for the purpose of performing specific tasks on our behalf. We do not share any personally identifying information with them without your explicit consent. We do not give them permission to disclose or use any of our data for any other purpose.
We may, from time to time, allow limited access to our data by external consultants and agencies for the purpose of analysis and service improvement. This access is only permitted for as long as necessary to perform a specific function. We only work with external agencies whose privacy policies align with ours.
We will refuse government and law enforcement requests for data if we believe a request is too broad or unrelated to its stated purpose. However, we may cooperate if we believe the requested information is necessary and appropriate to comply with legal process, to protect our own rights and property, to protect the safety of the public and any person, to prevent a crime, or to prevent what we reasonably believe to be illegal, legally actionable, or unethical activity.
We do not otherwise share or supply personal information to third parties. We do not sell or rent your personal information to marketers or third parties.
Limits of Our Policy
This privacy policy only covers FFTF's own collecting and handling of data. We only work with partners, affiliates and third-party providers whose privacy policies align with ours, however we cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices.
Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we have no control over the content and policies of those sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their respective privacy practices.
Security
We take security of your data seriously. Therefore, once we receive your transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Unfortunately, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. You remain responsible for the security of your computer at all times.
Cookie Policy
We use "cookies" to collect information about you and your activity across our site. A cookie is a small piece of data that our website stores on your computer, and accesses each time you visit, so we can understand how you use our site. This helps us serve you content based on preferences you have specified.
This cookie policy is part of FFTF's privacy policy, and covers the use of cookies between your device and our Site. We also provide basic information on third-party services we may use, who may also use cookies as part of their service, though they are not covered by our policy.
If you don't wish to accept cookies from us, you should instruct your browser to refuse cookies from https://www.endfatigue.com, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired content and services.
What Is a Cookie?
A cookie is a small piece of data that a website stores on your device when you visit, typically containing information about the website itself, a unique identifier that allows the site to recognise your web browser when you return, additional data that serves the purpose of the cookie, and the lifespan of the cookie itself.
Cookies are used to enable certain features (e.g., logging in), to track site usage (e.g., analytics), to store your user settings (e.g., timezone, notification preferences), and to personalise your content (e.g., advertising, language).
Cookies set by the website you are visiting are normally referred to as "first-party cookies," and typically only track your activity on that particular site. Cookies set by other sites and companies (i.e., third parties) are called "third-party cookies," and can be used to track you on other websites that use the same third-party service.
Types of Cookies and How We Use Them
Essential Cookies
Essential cookies are crucial to your experience of a website, enabling core features like user logins, account management, shopping carts and payment processing. We use essential cookies to enable certain functions on our website.
Performance Cookies
Performance cookies are used in the tracking of how you use a website during your visit, without collecting personal information about you. Typically, this information is anonymous and aggregated with information tracked across all site users, to help companies understand visitor usage patterns, identify and diagnose problems or errors their users may encounter, and make better strategic decisions in improving their audience's overall website experience. These cookies may be set by the website you're visiting (first-party) or by third-party services. We use performance cookies on our site.
Functionality Cookies
Functionality cookies are used in collecting information about your device and any settings you may configure on the website you're visiting (like language and timezone settings). With this information, websites can provide you with customised, enhanced or optimised content and services. These cookies may be set by the website you're visiting (first-party) or by third-party service. We
use this type of cookie on our site.
Targeting/Advertising Cookies
Targeting/advertising cookies are used in determining what promotional content is more relevant and appropriate to you and your interests. Websites may use them to deliver targeted advertising or to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. This helps companies improve the effectiveness of their campaigns and the quality of content presented to you. These cookies may be set by the website you're visiting (first-party) or by third-party services. Targeting/advertising cookies set by third-parties may be used to track you on other websites that use the same third-party service. We do not use this type of cookie on our site.
Third-Party Cookies on Our Site
We may employ third-party companies and individuals on our websites—for example, analytics providers and content partners. We grant these third parties access to selected information to perform specific tasks on our behalf. They may also set third-party cookies in order to deliver the services they are providing. Third-party cookies can be used to track you on other websites that use the same third-party service. As we have no control over third-party cookies, they are not covered by FFTF's cookie policy.
Our Third-Party Privacy Promise
We review the privacy policies of all our third-party providers before enlisting their services to ensure their practices align with ours. We will never knowingly include third-party services that compromise or violate the privacy of our users.
How You Can Control or Opt Out of Cookies
If you do not wish to accept cookies from us, you can instruct your browser to refuse cookies from our website. Most browsers are configured to accept cookies by default, but you can update these settings to either refuse cookies altogether, or to notify you when a website is trying to set or update a cookie.
If you browse websites from multiple devices, you may need to update your settings on each individual device.
Although some cookies can be blocked with little impact on your experience of a website, blocking all cookies may mean you are unable to access certain features and content across the sites you visit.
Changes to This Policy
At our discretion, we may change our privacy policy to reflect current acceptable practices. We will take reasonable steps to let users know about changes via our website. If you are a registered user on our Site, we will notify you using the contact details saved in your account. Your continued use of this site after any changes to this policy will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information.
Your Rights and Responsibilities
As our user, you have the right to be informed about how your data is collected and used. You are entitled to know what data we collect about you, and how it is processed. You are entitled to correct and update any personal information about you, and to request this information be deleted. You may amend your account information at any time, using the tools provided in your account control panel.
You are entitled to restrict or object to our use of your data, while retaining the right to use your personal information for your own purposes. You have the right to opt out of data about you being used in decisions based solely on automated processing.
Feel free to contact us if you have any concerns or questions about how we handle your data and personal information.
Your Consent
By using the Site and submitting information, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by us as described above.
In addition, by using the Site, you acknowledge agreement that you accept any risk of potential adverse side effects that may arise from following any recommendations made at the Site, and that you release from liability any persons or entities affiliated with the Site, including but not limited to FFTF and Dr. Jacob Teitelbaum.
Further Information
Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to customerservice@endfatigue.com.
Shopping Cart Summary
Your shopping cart is empty.
With Auto Ship!
Ship monthly or only when needed!
Learn more »
What S.H.I.N.E.® Users Say
Read Testimonials
Dr. T Analyzes Your Health Here!
Get a Free Instant Analysis
Featured This Week
Sleep Tonight™
Buy Now $17.78
